<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on SD</title>
    <link>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on SD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Shaun Donachy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shaundonachy.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubeval Online</title>
      <link>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/kubeval-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/kubeval-online/</guid>
      <description>Validate Kubernetes (k8s) yaml files online. This project was inspired by and based on garethr&amp;rsquo;s kubeval. After attending his talk at Kubecon in December 2017 I put this together to make use of kubeval to perform validations by pasting into a web interface. Garethr&amp;rsquo;s kubeval already has a nice CLI you can use as part of a CI/CD system, and kubevalonline supplements this tool for use during the development process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2d-midpoint-displacement-rust</title>
      <link>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/2d-midpoint-displacement-rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/2d-midpoint-displacement-rust/</guid>
      <description>Scenery image generator written in rust Another project inspired by a blog post.
I was interested in working with Rust some more and it was an excuse to implement one of my favorite algorithms: Bresenham&amp;rsquo;s line drawing algorithm.
You can see an example of the output above. Many of the variables are defined as constants in main.rs. Try modifying the image size or colors and generate your own scenery. 😎 The source code is hosted on github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automaton Pi</title>
      <link>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/automaton-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/automaton-pi/</guid>
      <description>.centerVid{text-align:center;}
A raspberry pi project The Automaton Pi project was created while I was studying machine learning with my fellow hackers Mack and Ljiljana and we wanted a hands-on project to work on.
Our idea If we can do object detection with a Raspberry Pi camera and use that same RPi to drive the vehicle, then we can create an autonomous RC car. Simple.
The platform First, we needed to get the platform ready, and the platform was our vehicle-mounted RPi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragenvoy Ludum Dare 26</title>
      <link>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/dragenvoy-ld-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaundonachy.com/projects/dragenvoy-ld-26/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a fan of game jams and indie game development. One of the game jams I participated in was Ludum Dare 26 with the theme of minimalism. I was reminded of one of the most minimal games &amp;ldquo;snake&amp;rdquo; which folks used to play on the tiny lcd screens of their ancient mobile dumb-phones.
Tools I used Unity and C# to develop the game over a weekend. The concept was to build a snake game but use physics to determine the movement of the snake.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>